in a univers that's INF like many
the there are parall worlds where every
possibility lives so a planet Somewhere
Out There their history the same as ours
is
written the only difference is
that everyone a
kitten KY his just like ours ky ky
driving cars KY somewhere in Quantum
space
mathematic had to take place Kitty world
wars and kitty Mass gra colonialism and
kitty slaves it's Kitty history
somewhere out of the
Stars Just Like Us Kitty Columbus until
he saw land but then quickly got off so
he could poop in the sand they formed
the first kitty cities and kitty towns
then they wake up at night just to run
around they had their own little kitty
Civil War but found some string and
forgot what they were fighting for it
King history and it's just like
us little kitty JFK got killed by Kitty
Lyndon Johnson and the CIA then Lyndon
double down on Kitty Vietnam and they
bought more helicopters and kitty bombs
from a company where his wife was the
main stoper and they made a kitty
Fortune for the war was over Kitty
history C planed like
ours a little kitty in the CIA who
helped kill Kennedy in Dallas that day
did so darn well that his career got a
push a kitty D George HW Bush he's made
CIA director and vice president's next
all while getting Kitty Saudi Arabian
checks Kitty hisory Kitty's Tak
[Music]
charge Kitty Bush Waits his turn to
ascend to his throne gets his cronies in
power Kitty USA overthrown the kitty
saies know how he can repay his death so
he starts a war with Thea there number
one bread but Kitty Sadam is not ejected
and the very next year Kitty George
isn't reelected Kitty history kitties
need a new
star Kitty Bush gets his son's jobs as
Governor then one steal the election for
the other new kitty bush has got to
finish the Saudi Mission so it has a
report made by a commission this is to
start a new war as far as we can attest
you need a new kitty Pro Harbor and we
all know the rest Kitty history exactly
like our
[Music]
KY in the SP Loops KY and KY banking
groups Kitty KY surveillance dates Kitty
terrorists on Kitty government pay Kitty
hist come on and sing six Kitty
companies run
everything Kitty history somewhere out
in the
[Applause]
Stars
I'm in church I'm in church oh God
please help me this is the worst I'm
high in church I'm in church I'm high as
hell